(Penny:)...for, you know, everything.
(Raj:)Please, Penny, let me.
(Raj:)We've decided to let our crazy,
wonderful night together...
(Raj:)...be just one
of those memories you have...
(Raj:)...and can call to mind when you're
feeling blue or you're in the shower.
(Penny:)Hey, what you doing, quick draw?
(Raj:)Sorry. Go on.
Anyways, I wanted you to know that I've
been taking a really hard look at things...
(Penny:)...and come to the conclusion
I have to stop kidding myseIf.
(Penny:)I suck at acting.
(Penny:)It's time for me
to move back to Nebraska.
- You're leaving?
- Yeah.
What are you gonna do in Nebraska?
(Penny:)I don't know. Maybe teach acting.
(Penny:)Sorry. Hold on. Hello?
(Leonard:)I hope you're not doing this
because of you and me...
...because I have a girIfriend
and you're a single...